gurl.ly 2019-05-07

# Privacy

Cookies are small text files placed on a Device when the Device is used to visit the Service or the Site. We may place cookies or similar files on your Device for security purposes, to facilitate site navigation and to personalize your experience while using the Service, such as showing you specific offer(s) that we think will be of interest to you. We also use cookies in order to keep you logged in to the Service if you register with us. Cookies allow us to collect technical and navigational information, such as browser type, time spent on the Service and pages visited. Cookies may include a Device Identifier along with information about the particular type of content in which you have shown interest. Cookies also allow us to select which content is most likely to appeal to you and display that content while you are using the Service. When interacting with the Service, if you click on a link to one of our promoted offer(s), the customer sponsoring the promoted link may place a cookie on your Device as well, in which case you will be subject to their privacy policy. Please note that you are subject to the privacy policies of each site you visit, in addition to ours. If you click on a link to visit a site where the Service is not installed, you are subject only to that site’s privacy policy while visiting that site, and not to this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer not to accept cookies, you can do this by activating the settings on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies, please be aware that some functions and features of the Service may not work properly because we may not be able to recognize and associate you with your account.

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service. 

###### Third-Party Links and Sites:

This Site may link to other websites operated by third parties. We have no control over these linked sites, each of which have separate privacy and data collection practices independent of GETSURL network. We are not responsible for and do not endorse or accept any responsibility for the availability, contents, products, services or use of any third party site, any website accessed from a third party site or any changes or updates to such sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk. You acknowledge that you bear all risks associated with access to and use of content provided on a third party site and agree that we are not responsible for any loss or damage you may incur from dealing with such a third party site. You should contact the site administrator for the applicable third party site if you have any concerns regarding such links or the content located on any such third party site. 

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

###### How we use the Information we collect

We use the information we collect about and from you for a variety of business purposes, including for example: to respond to your questions and requests; to provide you with access to certain functions and features of the Service; to provide and maintain your platform account(s); to verify your identity; to communicate with you about your account and activities using the Service and, in our sole discretion for marketing or solicitation purposes, to communicate changes to one of our policies; to tailor content or offer(s) we serve you; to improve the Service for internal business purposes; to process applications and transactions; and for other lawful purposes we may disclose at the time you provide your Personal Information or to which you otherwise consent.

We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees,   
to the extent that we are required to do so by law;   
in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings.  
Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third parties. 

Your Privacy Rights and Choices We will provide reasonable opportunity for individuals to access, update, or delete Personal Information about them that we have in our possession. We will not use Personal Information provided to us for purposes incompatible with the purpose for which it was provided without obtaining authorization from the subject of the information. Individuals’ principal rights under data protection law are:  
(a) the right to access;  
(b) the right to rectification;  
(c) the right to erasure;  
(d) the right to restrict processing;  
(e) the right to object to processing;  
(f) the right to data portability;  
(g) the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and  
(h) the right to withdraw consent.
